

# TANET LIMSUMANGKOLKUL

#### CONTACT

- 09
  - 0982846992
- - jaytanet@gmail.com
- 9 56 road rama2 alley 51 Subdistrict thakam District Bang Khun Thian Bangkok 10150

## **SKILL**

- Javascript
- php
- Html
- MySql
- SQL Server
- JQuery
- Css
- Node.js
- React
- Express.
- Postman

- Test Case
- Test Scenario
- Application Testing
- Websites Testing
- Vending Machines Testing
- Robot Framework

## **LANGUAGE**

- English
- Thai

## **PROFILE**

My major is Information System with experience in project, internship, activities, leaned in university and work. That gave me skills in work experience, communication teamwork and coding skill. I can apply my education and skills to software development.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Programmer | Bizpotential co. ltd

(Mar 2022 - Nov 2022)

• The systems that I am responsible for are

**CRA ERP EDU (MA)**. is an educational system of Chulabhorn Royal Academy.

MUIC (MA). is the educational system of Mahidol University.

SIRIRAJ, an education system for Siriraj Hospital,

**TSRI\_HR**, which is a welfare system for the Office of the Higher Education Commission,

**MRTA\_HR**, a welfare system for the Mass Rapid Transit Authority of Thailand.

My responsibilities include adding new functions or modifying the systems according to customer requirements, Send up email notifications in various formats, creating functions to import data from Excel to the database, and generating Word files in different formats.

# sabuy infrastructure co. ltd | QA/Tester

(April 2023 - July 2023)

- I have written test cases to test websites, SBM Wallet, KEX Wallet, Sabuy Wash application and vending machine.
- Write test results and Write down the found defect.
- Report results and prepare documents for the next test.

## **EDUCATION**

# *Mittraphon Business Administration* (2012-2016)

• Business Computer

# Rajamangala University of Technology Krungthep (2017-2020)

• Information System